[{
  "front": "hádat se",
  "back": "to argue"
}, {
  "front": "hádat",
  "back": "to guess"
}, {
  "front": "domluvit se",
  "back": "to agree"
}, {
  "front": "opalovat se",
  "back": "to tan"
}, {
  "front": "chodít",
  "back": "to walk"
}, {
  "front": "bojít se",
  "back": "to be afraid"
}, {
  "front": "vyhrát",
  "back": "to win"
}, {
  "front": "sprchovat se",
  "back": "to take a shower"
}, {
  "front": "umýt",
  "back": "to wash"
}, {
  "front": "učesat se",
  "back": "to brush hair"
}, {
  "front": "zavřít",
  "back": "to close"
}, {
  "front": "vrátit se",
  "back": "to return"
}, {
  "front": "vyspat se",
  "back": "to get some sleep"
}, {
  "front": "vzbudit",
  "back": "to wake"
}, {
  "front": "otevřít",
  "back": "to open"
}, {
  "front": "ustlat",
  "back": "to make a bed"
}, {
  "front": "vyvětrat",
  "back": "to air"
}, {
  "front": "odejít",
  "back": "to leave"
}, {
  "front": "zapnout",
  "back": "to turn on"
}, {
  "front": "vypnout",
  "back": "to turn off"
}, {
  "front": "vybrat",
  "back": "to choose"
}, {
  "front": "dát",
  "back": "to give"
}, {
  "front": "uvařit",
  "back": "to cook"
}, {
  "front": "vymyslet",
  "back": "to invent"
}, {
  "front": "vzít",
  "back": "to take"
}, {
  "front": "přinést",
  "back": "to bring"
}, {
  "front": "najít",
  "back": "to find"
}, {
  "front": "vyhledat",
  "back": "to search"
}, {
  "front": "položit",
  "back": "to lay"
}, {
  "front": "nakrájet",
  "back": "to slice"
}, {
  "front": "namazat",
  "back": "to grease"
}, {
  "front": "posolit",
  "back": "to salt"
}, {
  "front": "nalít",
  "back": "to infuse"
}, {
  "front": "zapnout",
  "back": "to turn on"
}, {
  "front": "tisknu",
  "back": "to printing"
}, {
  "front": "zavolat",
  "back": "to call"
}, {
  "front": "rozsvěcet",
  "back": "to turn on"
}]